http://www.theproblemsite.com/privacy

The Problem Site Quote Puzzler Tile Puzzler LoginfalseLoading profile...Member loginUser namePasswordI'm new here!I lost my passwordLogged in as: Log me outModify my profilePassword recoveryEmail addressReturn to login screenNew member.NewsDailyGamesLessonsProblemsReferenceResourcesPrintablesGo Pro!horizontalAll gamesDaily GamesMath gamesWord gamesStrategy and PuzzlesArt GamesVocabulary GamesJunior Edition GamesQuizzesAll problemsHigh School MathMAML ProblemsBrain FoodCalculus ProblemsLoony PhysicsPro ProblemsGetting StartedPro Control PanelVirtual Classroom Play My FavoritesSelect My Favorites Pro Help/privacy
This site is one of many sites in the Virtu Software family of educational and informational websites. This site conforms to the following Privacy Policy.Privacy Policy
This site will not collect any personally identifiable information from you without your express knowledge and consent. Examples of personally identifiable information which may be collected from you include: your email address, used to create and verify a user account, or a mailing address used for processing payments and/or shipping products.
This site may also ask you for your birthdate. If collected, this information is used for the protection of children under the age of 13, who are not permitted to post in the public forums, or display personal information in any public portion of the website.
We value your privacy, and if any personally identifiable information is collected from you, it will never be given, sold, or distributed to any third party without your express permission.*
Third-party advertising companies may be used to serve advertisements when you visit this site. These advertising companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
*At Virtu Software, we vehemently despise privacy violations and the mayhem they can cause. We have even created an Anti Spam Site to warn people about the many uses and abuses of personally identifiable information online. You can rest assured that we will treat your personal information with all diligence and privacy.
Understanding Coronavirus Spread
Exponential Growth and Coronavirus
A Question and Answer session with Professor Puzzler about the math behind infection spread.
Blogs on This Site
Book Scrounger
Reviews and book lists - books we love!
Ask Professor Puzzler
The site administrator fields questions from visitors.
Like us on Facebook to get updates about new resourcesHomePro MembershipAboutPrivacy/
